topons.com 2012-12-25

# Security and privacy - Topons launches Online Marketplace

**Security and privacy :**

Thank you for visiting the website ("site") of topons.com. Topons is committed to respecting your privacy and protecting your personal information. Except as indicated below, Topons will not sell, rent or share any personally identifiable information that you provide without your consent.

**Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

Our web servers automatically capture non-personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your domain name, the IP address of the webpage from which you enter our site, the pages that you visit on our site, the click-through rates, and the amount of time that you spend here. However, the individual user will remain anonymous. We may use and analyze this data for trends and to improve our site. Any non-personally identifiable information that we give to third parties will be provided in aggregate form only.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

When you engage in activities such as registering or purchasing our products, you may be required to submit personal information to topons. This information will include data such as your name, address, phone number, fax number, and email address. Topons will not provide any personally identifiable information to any third parties without your consent. However, Topons reserves the right to provide personally identifiable information to third parties if topons reasonably believes that this release of information is necessary to comply with legal requirements or legal process or to protect and defend the rights or property of topons.

**Respect children's privacy**

Topons does not knowingly collect or use information from children under the age of 18 without the consent of a parent or guardian. Elsewhere on this Site, you have represented and warranted that you are either 18 years of age or are using the Site with the supervision of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 18 , please do not submit any personal information to us, and rely on a parent or guardian to assist you when using the Site.

**Cookies**

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies work as your identification card and may record passwords, preferences and purchases. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.

**Other Websites and Links**

This site contains links to other websites. If you choose to use any of these links, you will be leaving topons’s website and going to a new website. Protection of your privacy at these linked sites will be governed by the privacy policy at that site. You should take the time to read the privacy policies at these sites. Topons is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites or the use of any information that you provide.

**Security**

If you send credit card information to topons, Topons will encrypt this information between your computer and our server. Other information that you send to this site, including email messages, will not be encrypted unless we keep you informed. Although our site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information that is under our control, topons cannot guarantee complete security.

**Updates to this policy**

To keep you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any changes or updates to this Privacy Notice on this Site and encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to time. Please contact us with any questions about the Privacy Notice.
